const quiz1data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "I'll give you an umbrella if it ___.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "rains", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "rained", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "",
      help1: ""
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Coffee ____ sweet if we add sugar.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "will taste", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "tastes", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use Zero Conditional when the result of the condition is always true. We are talking about a general truth, not a particular situation. The structure is: ",
      help1: " if + present simple, present simple"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "If you miss the train, you __ be late to go to your job.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "will", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "would", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "",
      help1: ""
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "",
      help1: ""
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "If we leave now, we ___ be home on time for dinner.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "will", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "would", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "",
      help1: ""
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "if you mix blue and yellow, you ___ green.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "get", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "will get", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use Zero Conditional when the result of the condition is always true. It's a fact. The structure is: ",
      help1: " if + present simple, present simple"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "",
      help1: ""
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "If I ___ to bed late, I will be tired tomorrow.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "go", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "went", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "",
      help1: ""
    },
    
]

export default quiz1data